consumeractiongroup.co.uk 2013-06-15

# - The Consumer Forums

An excellent guide for the layperson in how to use the County Court - a must if you are intending to start a claim.

£19.99 + £1.50 (P&P)

* * *

Written by John Kruse, one of the leading experts on Bailiff Law, this consumer friendly guide is essential reading for anyone who comes into contact with a bailiff. 

The book is easy to understand and clearly explains the rights a bailiff has, and also what they cannot do when collecting debts and repossessing goods etc.

£13.95 + £2.00 (P&P)

[Reclaim the Right Ltd. - reg. 05783665 in the UK

reg. office:  
923 Finchley Road  
London   
NW11 7PE

](http://www.consumeractiongroup.co.uk/forum/feedback.php)

| 

    THE CONSUMER FORUMS PRIVACY POLICY
    
    This policy applies to all forums operated by Reclaim the Right Limited, and includes (but is not limited to) the Consumer Action Group, 
    Bank Action Group, Debt Action Group and the Consumer Forums. Hereafter, these are referred to as the Consumer Forums.

    WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS
    
    Your privacy is a very important matter, and is taken very seriously by the Consumer Forums. Please read the following to learn more 
    about our privacy policy. In addition to our own attitude to the importance of your privacy, we are also registered with the Information 
    Commissioner under The Data Protection Act. Our Data Protection Registration number is Z9440256

    HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
    
    This policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive, including information relating to your past use of the 
    Consumer Forums. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or 
    telephone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
    
    This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the Consumer Forums, or Reclaim the Right Limited, do not own or control, 
    or to people that we do not employ or manage.
    
    Because of our obligations under the Data Protection Act, we conform with all UK and European standards for the protection of privacy.

    INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
    
    The Consumer Forums collect personal information when you register with any of our forums or buy our products. When you register we may 
    ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, postal code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. 
    When you register with the Consumer Forums, and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
    
    The Consumer Forums collects information about your transactions with us, and with some of our business partners, including information 
    about your use of any financial products and services that we might offer.
    
    The Consumer Forums automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Consumer 
    Forums cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.
    
    The Consumer Forums uses information for the following general purposes: to customise the advertising and content you see, fulfil your 
    requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for our internal 
    purposes.
    
    The Consumer Forums does not contact its registered users or its visitors about any products or services other than through its newsletter 
    which has been subscribed to as a part of the forum registration process. The Consumer Forums does not contact any person if that person 
    has not registered as a forum user - even if that person has bought products or services through our website pages.

    CHILDREN
    
    The Consumer Forums does not differentiate between adults and children in relation to its data use policy, and the same safeguards are 
    applied regardless of age. However we remind parents to be vigilant over their children's use of the Internet, and if they have any concerns 
    about the Consumer Forums websites they should use the "Complaints about Website Content" button on the left side of the main forum webpage.

    UNSOLICITED TELEPHONE CALLS
    
    If you receive an unsolicited telephone call offering legal services from any individual or company claiming to be from the Consumer Forums, 
    Consumer Action Group, CAG, or any similar name, please email admin@consumeractiongroup.co.uk and do not agree to any service that may be 
    offered.
    
    We do not do this.
    
    Any company offering legal services in these circumstances will not be authorised by the Consumer Forums, and will be acting in breach of 
    the law.

    INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE
    
    The Consumer Forums does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people except under the following circumstances:
    
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected 
    fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Consumer Forums terms of use, or as 
    otherwise required by law.
    * We may transfer information about you if The Consumer Forums is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify 
    you (by your registered email address) before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
    * The Consumer Forums do not display targeted advertisements based on personal information.
    * Targeted advertisements on The Consumer Forums website are context based, and are not related to any information which we may hold about
     you as an individual.
    * The Consumer Forums do not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted advert. However, 
    by interacting with or viewing an advert you are consenting to the
    possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the advert. The Consumer Forums
     advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stockbrokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial 
    companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

    COOKIES
    
    The Consumer Forums may set and access cookies that it has placed on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to 
    these cookies.

    YOUR ABILITY TO EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES
    
    You can edit your Consumer Forums Account Information, at any time through the User Control Panel (USER CP). Registered users can unsubscribe 
    from our newsletter by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.
    
    We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the the Consumer Forums, such as service announcements, administrative 
    messages and the Consumer Forums Newsletter. Whilst You have the opportunity to opt out of receiving this information, where we consider 
    that we have to let you know some important information such as account changes, policy or rule changes etc, then we may contact you anyway.

    CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY
    
    We limit access to personal information about you to employees, and volunteers appointed to the site team, who we believe reasonably need 
    to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
    
    We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with Data Protection Act regulations to protect personal information 
    about you.

    FUTURE UPDATES
    
    The Consumer Forums may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by 
    sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Consumer Forums account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

    QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS
    
    If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us at:
    
    Reclaim the Right Limited, 923 Finchley Road, London. NW11 7PE
    
    Effective Date: July  05, 2006

consumeractiongroup.co.uk   

[Reclaim the Right Ltd. - reg.05783665 in the UK reg. office:- 923 Finchley Road London NW11 7PE](http://www.consumeractiongroup.co.uk/forum/feedback.php)  
  
---|---
